

Tommaso Padovan **Computer Scientist**



5 July 1993



Rhönring 141 Darmstadt, 64289 Germany



+39 3484655214



tommaso.pado@gmail.com

About me ——

Alice is a sensible prepubescent girl from a wealthy English family who finds herself in a strange world ruled by imagination and fantasy. Alice feels comfortable with her identity and has a strong sense that her environment is comprised of clear, logical, and consistent rules and features. Alice's familiarity with the world has led one critic to describe her as a "disembodied intellect". Alice displays great curiosity and attempts to fit her diverse experiences into a clear understanding of the world.

Skills —

Java

polite

outgoing

good manners

pursuer of rabbits

lovely*4 narcissistic*3

(*)[The skill scale is from 0 (Fundamental Awareness) to 6 (Expert).]

Education

2017

	Specializing in Computer Vision, CUDA and Game Technology at "TU Dark stadt" 1		
2016	Master degree in Computer Science At "Università degli Studi di Padova" ²	Padova (Italy)	
2013-2016	Bachelor degree in Computer Science Achieved with 100/110 at "Università degli Studi di Padova" ²	Padova (Italy)	
2007-2012	High school	Treviso (Italy)	

Darmstadt

Master degree (Erasmus) in Computer Science

Lyceum of Sciences and Informatics

Work Experience							
2016-2017	Developer at "Vision Lab Apps srl" ³ Android + back-end of streaming application for smartpho	Part-time Job ones and glasses.					
2016	Developer at "Vic World Wide" ⁴ Prototype app for "world 3D reconstruction" using Google on mobile devices.	Stage -Tango framework					
2015-2016	Developer at "EasyApp srl" ⁵ Front-end and back-end for ERPs.	Freelance Job					
IT Skills							

• C++

Java

php

Programming languages

Strong knowledge in procedural, object-oriented, concurrent, functional and actorbased programming paradigms.

Strong experience with:

Scala (and akka)

Discreet experience with:

• CUDA C++ • Python

· Javascript/NodeJS

Julia

Haskell

• Go

Tools and frameworks

- · Good practice with IDEs and frameworks as JetBrains Suite, QT, Android Studio, Laravel, etc.
- · Familiarity with Git/GitFlow both with CLI and graphical interfaces; basic understanding of Subversion and Mercurial.
- Teamwork experience acquired during academic and professional projects; good skills in using work management-tools such as teamwork.com, Trello, GanttProject, Slack, etc.
- Good knowledge of UML graphical language and UML-editors (e.g. Astah).
- Good knowledge of Google Tango⁶ framework for augmented reality in mobile
- Some experience with game-engine such as Unreal Engine and Unity3D.

Some projects

- Actobase: NoSQL database based on the actor model using Scala-lang with akka. Developed in a group of seven during an academic project. Source code available at: https://github.com/SweeneyThreads/Actorbase.
- Baobab: Small set of Python scripts for simple neurological image analysis. Developed for/in collaboration with a PhD in psychiatry. https://github. com/TommasoPadovan/Baobab
- Other academic projects:

https://github.com/TommasoPadovan/ProgettiUniPDTriennale

¹ https://www.informatik.tu-darmstadt.de

²http://www.unipd.it

³http://www.visionlabapps.com

⁴http://vicworldwide.com/it/your-eyes-worldwide

⁵http://www.easyappsrl.it

⁶https://developers.google.com/tango